{
    "subject": "Pakistan_Atomic_Energy_Commission",
    "predicate": "isLocatedIn",
    "object": "Islamabad",
    "human_readable": "The Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission is located in Islamabad.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9545321464538574,
            "question": "Where is the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9503752589225769,
            "question": "Where is the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9210312366485596,
            "question": "What is the location of the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9209753274917603,
            "question": "Which country's Atomic Energy Commission is based in Islamabad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8164538145065308,
            "question": "In what city can you find the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7637003064155579,
            "question": "Name the city that serves as the base for the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7042741775512695,
            "question": "What city houses the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4136790335178375,
            "question": "What organization operates within Islamabad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4056073725223541,
            "question": "Islamabad is home to which important organization in Pakistan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3934570550918579,
            "question": "Islamabad is the headquarters of which organization?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission is located in Islamabad.",
            "html": "yago_25388_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Islamabad is home to which important organization in Pakistan?",
            "html": "yago_25388_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What organization operates within Islamabad?",
            "html": "yago_25388_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city houses the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission?",
            "html": "yago_25388_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25388_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25388_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25388_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25388_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25388_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25388_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25388_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25388_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25388_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25388_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that the Pakistan Atomic Energy Commission (PAEC) General Hospital is located in Islamabad, specifically on Faqir Aipee Road. This supports the statement that the PAEC, which has a hospital in Islamabad, is located in Islamabad."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}